<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BCR FM</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Menu opened</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Menu closed</string>
    <string name="action_SocialMedia">Share on Social Media</string>


    <string name="home">Listen Live to BCR FM</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact BCR FM</string>
    <string name="about">About BCRFM</string>
    <string name="website">BCRFM.IE</string>
    <string name="fb">BCR FM on Facebook</string>
    <string name="tweet">BCR FM on Twitter</string>
    <string name="schedule">BCR FM Show Schedule</string>

    <string name="search_title">Find Show by name eg <i>"The Double Espresso"</i></string>

    <string name="developer">About the Developer</string>
    
    <string name="socialMediaMenu">Social Media Menu</string>

    <string name="developerinfo">This app was developed by Patrick Melia. Patrick has graduated with Bsc Hons Software Development degree from IT Sligo.
        \n
        \n
        \nPatrick is a committee member and is co-host of The Double Espresso since July 2014. He has been involved in community/volunteer work from the age of 16
        when he joined the Ballina Salmon Festival (PRO during the Golden Anniversary), Cub Scout leader since 2010.
        \n
        \n
        \nNeed to contact him? If so, click the Email ME button below :D <b>PS</b> keep an eye out for our new website (Hopefully between Oct \ Nov 2015) ;)
        \n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="hello">BCRfm is a not-for-profit community radio station to serve Ballina and its outskirts.

        We are a voice for the community, run by the community.

        A dedicated committee of young and old who are passionate about radio and

        the place they call home.  We want to renew the vibrancy of Ballina and showcase what

        it and its outskirts has to offer.

        \n
        \n
        \n<b>Send Us Your Music!</b>
        \n
        \nBCRfm loves music and we aim to get as much great and varied music on the airwaves as possible.

        BCRfm is committed to showcasing music from Irish composers, singer songwriters and local bands across the programme schedule, with emphasis on those who would not yet have reached national fame.

        We will regularly feature demo discs from local groups, individual artists and have a one hour weekly programme dedicated to local bands and musicians.

        Local bands, choirs both adult and children’s will on occasion play live in the studio.
        We are happy to air recorded music, live sessions, gig recordings or interviews, feel free to get in touch.
    </string>

</resources>
